Information Studies, Department of; Records ua671
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration and Faculty, 1912-2001; 1; 6.9 cubic ft.
  - Library School Organization, 1965; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Library Services to the Handicapped - 032-0820A ( Whalen), 1977; Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Library Traineeship Program, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mail Regulations, 1978-1979; 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Major Field Examination, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Marco, Guy, 1955-1959; 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Martha C. Pritchard Fund, 1951-1955; 1960; 1962-1963; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mary E. Hall Fund., 1931-1932; 1936-1937; 1939-1941; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Masters Program Proposal, ca. 1949 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mathews, Dr. Elmer, 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - McGaw, Dr. Howard, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mini-Courses, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Minority Group Traineeship Program, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Name Change, 1970-1971; 1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1979-1980; 1982-1984; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Office Inventories, 1926; 1928; 1931-1942; 1944-1947 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Office Quarters, 1940; 1943; 1951; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Office Quarters, 1940; 1943; 1951; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Open House, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Orientation, 1973-1974; ca.1975; 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Peer Review Process, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Personnel Committee, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Personnel - NTP, 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Office, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Performance Evaluation, 1976; 1979; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Physical Plant Department, 1979; 1982; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Pilot Program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Planning ( University), 1960; 1976-1977; 1979; 1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Position Opening, 1958; Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Possible Lectures, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Press Material, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Pritchard, Martha C. - Correspondence, 1912; 1921; 1926-1934 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pritchard, Martha C. - Correspondence, 1935-1939; 1941-1942; 1948; 1954-1955; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Profile - University, 1971-1975; 1977-1980; 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Programs - New, 1953; Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Promotion and Continuing Appointments, 1980-1981; 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Promotion Criteria, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Property Control System, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Proposal for Distribution of Discretionary Salary Increase, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Proposal Training for Gerentology, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Public Safety Department - SUNY, 1980; 1982-1983; 1987 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Public Service Training Program Enrollment Rosters, RESTRICTED, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Publication/ Printing Guidelines and Costs, 1978-1980; 1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Publications - SLIS, 1966; 1978-1984; 1986; Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Publications - SLIS, 1966; 1978-1984; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 1)
  - Publications - University, 1978; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Puerto Rico Project, 1966; 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Puerto Rico Project, 1968-1970 (Oversized 12, Folder 2)
  - Purchasing Procedures, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Questionnaire for Graduate - Completed (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Questionnaire for Graduate - Completed (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Reaccreditation Committees, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Reaccreditation Committees - Facilities, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Reaccreditation Committees - Faculty, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Reaccreditation Committees - Goals and Objectives, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Reaccreditation Committees - Governance, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Reaccreditation Committees - Students, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Records Management Fellowships, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Recruitment, 1977-1978; 1981 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Recruitment of Students, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Registration, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Relocation - SLIS ( 1 of 2), 1954; 1960-1971; 1974-1976; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Relocation - SLIS ( 2 of 2), 1954; 1960-1971; 1974-1976; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Research Office for, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Research Committee, 1977; 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Research and Educational Development Office of, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Research Grant 020-7324A ( Burgess), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Research Grant - Film Literature Index 320-0967A (Aceto), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Research Grant - Film Literature Index 320-0967A (Aceto), 1977-1978 (Oversized 12, Folder 3)
  - Research Grant Proposal - " Meeting Needs of Librarians", 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Research Grants ( Misc), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Retraining Grants, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Robinson, Everlyn RESTRICTED, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller College, 1983; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller College - Union and Name Change, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - R.R. Bowker Co. - Correspondence, 1951; 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Safety, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships, State Recipients, 1957-1959; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - School Advisory Planning Committee, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Second Field, SLIS ( Undergraduate, Miror), 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Self-Study, 1972-1973; 1979; 1981; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Seminars and Special Courses, 1971-1974; 1976-1978; 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Seymour, William, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Sixth Year Program ( Campus Certificate), 1976-1980; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - SLIS Bulletins, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - SLIS Bulletins, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - SLIS Bulletins, 1978-1980; ca.1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Special Programs - Accreditation (1 of 2), 1952; 1961; 1964-1969; 1971-1972; Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Special Programs - Accreditation (2 of 2), 1952; 1961; 1964-1969; 1971-1972; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Special Programs - Clerical Training, 1955; 1960; Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Special Programs - Computers in Library Science, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Special Programs - Faculty Exhange, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Special Programs - Foreign Area Materials, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Special Programs - John Cotton - Dana Lectures, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Special Programs - Library Serviec and Congressional Action, 1962; 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Special Programs - Library Survey, Misc., 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Special Programs - Library Technician Program, 1966; 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Special Programs - Medical Literature, 1957; 1961-1963; Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Special Programs - NDEA 1966 Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Special Programs - Public Librarian Training Grant, 1965-1967; 1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Special Programs - Research, 1958-1963; 1966; Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Special Programs - School Librarianship, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Special Programs - Vermont Summer Institute, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Stallman, Ester, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - State Education Department - Visitation, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - State University of New York, 1953; 1956; 1964 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Statement of Policy and Procedures, 1926-1935 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Stewart, Nathaniel, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Student Affairs Committee, 1974-1976; 1978-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Student Affairs Committee - Colloquium Series, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Student Directories, 1936-1947 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Student Evalutations RESTRICTED, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Student Guide, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Student Hardbook, 1984; 1986; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Student Projects, 1930-1936; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subscription Books Bulletin - List of Subscription Books and Sets (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sullivan, James, 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session - Admission Standards and Bulletins, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Summer Session - Allocations, 1971-1972; 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session - Catalogue Material and Schedules, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session - Correspondence with Director, 1931-1934 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SUNYA Annual Fund (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Symposium: Reading/The American Family/Human Development/Pursuit of Happiness (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Tests and Measurements, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Thesis - Format and Procedures (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, Lola, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Three-Year Plan, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Three-Year Plan, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Program (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - University Affairs, Office of (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - University Organization, 1964-1966; 1980-1982; Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - University Organization, 1964-1966; 1980-1982; Undated (Oversized 12, Folder 4)
  - UUP Agreement with State of New York (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Vaillancourt, Pauline, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Vershoor, Irving, 1961-1965; Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Webb, Mae (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Welsh, Helen, 1955-1957; 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Winton, Grace, 1935-1937; Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Work Projects Administration, 1933-1946 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Workshops, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Workshops, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Workshops (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Workshops, 1973-1977; 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Course Materials, 1927-1992; 2; 6.2 cubic ft.
  This series consists of both bound volumes (1927-1954) and folders (1963-1992) that each contain syllabi, assignment sheets, handouts, examinations, and other class material related to the courses taught by the Department of Information Studies and its various incarnations.
  - Course Outlines and Syllabi, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Course Outlines and Syllabi ( 1 of 3), 1971-1977; 1981-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Course Outlines and Syllabi ( 2 of 3), 1971-1977; 1981-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Course Outlines and Syllabi ( 3 of 3), 1971-1977; 1981-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - LIB 10 Libraries and Schools - Volume 1, 1927-1940 (Oversized 4, Item 1)
  - LIB 12 Cataloging - Volume 1, 1927-1935 (Oversized 4, Item 2)
  - LIB 12 Cataloging - Volume 2, 1934-1937 (Oversized 4, Item 3)
  - LIB 12 Cataloging - Volume 3, 1937-1940 (Oversized 4, Item 4)
  - LIB 13 Administration - Volume 1, 1927-1930 (Oversized 5, Item 1)
  - LIB 13 Administration - Volume 2, 1930-1933 (Oversized 5, Item 2)
  - LIB 13 Administration - Volume 3, 1933-1940 (Oversized 5, Item 3)
  - LIB 15 Field Work - Volume 1, 1927-1940 (Oversized 5, Item 4)
  - LIB 17 Children's Literature - Volume 1, 1927-1933 (Oversized 6, Item 1)
  - LIB 17 Children's Literature - Volume 2, 1933-1938 (Oversized 6, Item 2)
  - LIB 17 Children's Literature - Volume 3, 1938-1940 (Oversized 6, Item 3)
  - LIB 17 Children's Literature - Volume 4, 1940-1948 (Oversized 6, Item 4)
  - LIB 18 Book Collection - Volume 1, 1927-1931 (Oversized 7, Item 1)
  - LIB 18 Book Collection - Volume 2, 1931-1933 (Oversized 7, Item 2)
  - LIB 18 Book Collection - Volume 3, 1933-1935 (Oversized 7, Item 3)
  - LIB 18 Book Collection - Volume 4, 1935-1938 (Oversized 7, Item 4)
  - LIB 18 Book Collection - Volume 5, 1938-1940 (Oversized 8, Item 1)
  - LIB 19 Reading Guidance - Volume 1, 1935-1940 (Oversized 8, Item 2)
  - LIB 20 History of Books and Printing - Volume 1, 1938-1940 (Oversized 8, Item 3)
  - LIB 21 Elementary School Libraries - Volume 1, 1938-1940 (Oversized 8, Item 4)
  - LIB 099 Media Lab, 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LIB 122 Selection, 1940-1948 (Oversized 9, Item 1)
  - LIB 123 Reference, 1941-1948 (Oversized 9, Item 2)
  - LIB 203 Library Resources ( Mitchell) ( 1 of 2), 1978-1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - LIB 203 Library Resources ( Mitchell) ( 2 of 2), 1978-1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - LIB 203 Library Resources - Cole and Whalen, 1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - LIB 210 Libraries and Librarianship, LIB 219 Reading Guidance, LIB 220 History of Books, 1940-1948 (Oversized 10, Item 1)
  - LIB 212 Cataloging, LIB 213A Organization, LIB 213B Administration, LIB 321 Public Library Administration, 1940-1948 (Oversized 10, Item 2)
  - LIB 222 Book Selection, 1948-1954 (Oversized 3, Item 1)
  - LIB 271 History of American Children's Literature - Mitchell, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - LIB 301 Introduction to Librarianship - Mitchell, Weibol, Whalen, Lipetz, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - LIB 303 Organization of Information Sources - Mitchell, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - LIB 350 Library Research - Roberts, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - LIB 500 Computer Programming for Information Services, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - LIB 501 History of Books and Printing - Katz, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - LIB 501 History of Books and Printing - Clarkin, 1972; 1974-1977; 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - LIB 503 The Book in America - Clarkin, 1973-1974; 1977-1979; 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - LIB 536 Systems Analysis In the Information Enviroment - Klemoner, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - LIB 539 Online Database Searching - Burgess, 1981; 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - LIB 539 Online Database Searching - Walker ( 1 of 2), 1983-1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - LIB 539 Online Database Searching - Walker ( 2 of 2), 1983-1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - LIB 550 Film and Libraries - Aceto, 1971; 1973; 1975; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - LIB 571 Literature for Children - Lenz, Hodge, 1983; 1986; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - LIB 571 Literature for Children - Osini, 1983; 1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - LIB 571 Literature for Children - Patrick ( 1 of 2), 1977-1980; 1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - LIB 571 Literature for Children - Patrick ( 2 of 2), 1977-1980; 1982; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - LIB 571 Literature for Children - Ravenger, Sacks, Mesches, 1967; 1971; 1974-1975; 1977-1979; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - LIB 573 History of Children's literature - Mitchell, 1975; 1978; 1982-1985; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - LIB 578 Library Materials for Young Adults - Aceto ( 1 of 2), 1978-1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - LIB 578 Library Materials for Young Adults - Aceto ( 2 of 2), 1978-1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - LIB 578 Literature for Young Adults - Leach, Currin, 1974; 1981; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - LIB 601 The Information Enviroment - Farley, 1977-1981; 1983-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - LIB 601 The Information Enviroment - Aceto, Burgess, Johnson, Prentice, 1971; 1973; 1975-1976; 1979; 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - LIB 601 Information Environment - Aceto, Burgess, Johnson, Prentice, 1986; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - LIB 602 Recorded Knowledge and Society - Mitchell, 1972-1973; 1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - LIB 603 Information Processing - Walker, 1980-1982; 1985-1987; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - LIB 603 Information Processing - Farley, Hoyle, Llinas, Stevens ( 1 of 2), 1976-1977; 1982-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - LIB 603 Information Processing - Farley, Hoyle, Llinas, Stevens ( 2 of 2), 1976-1977; 1982-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - LIB 603 Information Processing - Snyder, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - LIB 604 Introduction to Bibliography - Clarkin, Hoyle, Saffody, 1974; 1977; 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - LIB 605 The Reference Process - Cole, Morehead, Whalen, 1973-1974; 1976; 1981-1982; 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - LIB 607 Information Technology and Library Automotion - Klempner, 1976; 1979-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - LIB 607 Information Technology and Library Information - Anable, Llinas, Saffady, Walker, 1975-1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - LIB 608 Research Methods - Arouson, Prentice, 1973-1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - LIB 611 Information Systems and Technology Applications - Hoyle, Jones, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - LIB 609 Analysis of Information Population - Lipetz, 1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - LIB 613 The Communication Process - Stevenson, Weinstein, 1974; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - LIB 614 Administration of Information Agencies - Farley, 1981-1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - LIB 614 Administration of Information Agencies - Piggford, Prentice, Vailliancourt, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - LIB 615 Library and Information Networks - Klempner, 1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - LIB 615 Library and Information Networks, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - LIB 616 Social and Political Aspects of Librarianship, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - LIB 618 Comparative Librarianship - Piggford, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - LIB 619 Special Libraries/ Information Centers - Vialiancourt, 1974; 1977-1978; 1980-1982; 1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - LIB 619 Medical Librarianship - Poland, Van Nortwick, 1976; 1980; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - LIB 622 Micrographics - Halsey, Saffady, 1975-1977; 1979; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - LIB 623 Bibliographic Databases - Burgess, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - LIB 623 Laws/ Landmark Cases/ Libraries/ Politics in New York State - Halsey, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - LIB 623 Library Media Skills - Halsey, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - LIB 623 Microcomputers in Libraries - Burgess, 1981-1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - LIB 623 OCLC Mini-Course: The Classified Catalog - Burgess, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - LIB 623 OCLC Mini - Course: Information Management, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - LIB 623 Online Cataloging Systems - Hoyle, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - LIB 624 Adult Library Services - Cassell, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - LIB 624 APL Programming for Libraries - Saffady, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - LIB 624 Basic Programming for Information problems - Burgess, 1983-1984; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - LIB 624 Curriculum - Linked Library and Information Skills - Halsey, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - LIB 624 Information Resources for Human Services - Whalen, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - LIB 624 The Literature of Technical Reports - Klempner, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - LIB 624 Networks: Role and Functions - Evans, 1979; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LIB 624 Survey of User Education - Mitchell, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LIB 625 Contemporary Reference Resources - Halsey, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - LIB 625 Curriculum Linked Library and Information Skills - Halsey, 1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - LIB 625 Design and Evaluation in User Education - Mitchell, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - LIB 625 Human Relations in Library and Information Center Management - Farley, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - LIB 625 Legal and Administrative Barriers to Access to Information - Klempner, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - LIB 626 Bibliographic Databases - Burgess, 1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - LIB 626 Legal and Administrative Barries to Access to Information - Klempner, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - LIB 626 Micrographics - Halsey, 1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - LIB 626 Mini - Courses - Whalen, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - LIB 626 Searching OCLC - Hoyle, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - LIB 626 Survey of User Education - Mitchell, 1983; 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - LIB 627 Design and Education in User Education - Mitchell, 1977; 1983; 1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - LIB 627 New Technologies in the School Library Media Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - LIB 627 OCLC Mini-Courses - Hoyle, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - LIB 628 Nonprint Classification - Halsey, 1976; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - LIB 628 Systems Analysis for Information Services - Regazzi, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - LIB 629 American Girls 1860-1920 - Mitchell, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - LIB 629 Law Legislation and Librarians - Halsey, 1976; 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - LIB 629 Library Media Skills Instruction - Halsey, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - LIB 629 Literature for Young Adults - Gillespie, Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - LIB 629 Micrographics - Halsey, 1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - LIB 629 Technology and Nonprint Resources - Halsey, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - LIB 632 Organization of Nonbook Materials - Klempner, 1974-1975; 1977; 1979-1981; Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - LIB 633 Information Storage and Retrieval - Klempner, Saffady, Walker, 1976-1977; Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - LIB 633 Information Storage and Retrieval - Lipetz, 1980-1983; 1986-1987; 1989; Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - LIB 635 Theory of Classifcation - Klempner, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - LIB 636 System Analysis and Library Automation - Walker, Heinritz, Lipetz, 1973; 1977; 1981-1982; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - LIB 639 Computer Based Bibliographic Searching - Burgess, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - LIB 639 Library Orientation and Instruction in the Academic Library, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - LIB 640 Abstractin and Indexing - Aceto, Hoyle, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - LIB 641 Information Services to Business - Burgess, 1980; 1983-1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - LIB 642 Advanced Online Cataloging - Hoyle, 1983-1984; 1986; Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - LIB 642 Comparative National Bibliography - Stevens, Hoyle, 1974; Undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - LIB 643 Information Sources in the Humanities - Hoyle, 1967; 1975-1979; 1986; 1988; 1990 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - LIB 643 Library Materials in the Humanities - Cole, 1969; 1973; Undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - LIB 644 Information Sources in the Social Sciences - Whalen, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - LIB 644 Library Materials in the Social Services - Halsey, Farley, 1975-1978; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - LIB 645 Information Sources in the Sciences - Vaillancourt, 1983; Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - LIB 646 Records Management - Whalen, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - LIB 647 Health Sciences Bibliography - Rees, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - LIB 647 Sources for Information on Statistics for the Health Sciences - Vailliancourt, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - LIB 651 Serials - Houle, 1979-1983; 1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - LIB 651 Serials - Katz, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - LIB 653 Documents and Publications of International Organizations - Morehead, 1972; 1978; 1980; 1982; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - LIB 653 Documents and Publications of International Organizations - Morehead, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - LIB 654 Contemporary Publishing - Vailliancourt, Cole, 1976-1978; 1980-1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - LIB 655 Rare Books - Clarkin, 1973; 1977; 1981-1984; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - LIB 656 Archives and Manuscripts - Cox, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - LIB 656 Archives and Manuscripts - Stewarts, Mills, Saffady, 1976-1978; 1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - LIB 656 Archives and Manuscripts - Whalen, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - LIB 658 Laws and Legislation Affecting Libraries - Halsey, 1978-1981; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - LIB 659 Information Systems in Human Serivces - Whalen, 1979-1981; 1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - LIB 660 National Information Policy - Morehead, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LIB 666 Abstracting and Indexing - Lipetz, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LIB 666 Advanced Online Systems - Walker, 1981; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - LIB 666 Archives - Saffady, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - LIB 666 Bibliographic Control of Serials - Hoyle, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - LIB 666 Cataloging Online - Hoyle, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)